    export interface Question {
        id:number,
        triviaQuestion: string,
        answer: string,
        optionOne:string,
        optionTwo:string,
        optionThree:string,
        optionFour:string,
    }

    export const questionData:Question[] = [
    {
      id: 1,
      triviaQuestion:
        "Disney's Animal Kingdom theme park opened in Florida in Which Year?",
      answer: "1998",
      optionOne: "1998",
      optionTwo: "1990",
      optionThree: "2004",
      optionFour: "2010",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      triviaQuestion: "Nemo ends up in a Tank in which sort of office?",
      answer: "Dentist",
      optionOne: "Home",
      optionTwo: "Garden",
      optionThree: "Cellular",
      optionFour: "Dentist",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      triviaQuestion:
        "What is the Name of Buzz and Woody's original owner in Toy Story?",
      answer: "Andy",
      optionOne: "David",
      optionTwo: "Andy",
      optionThree: "Marcus",
      optionFour: "Samuel",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      triviaQuestion: "What is the Last Name of the Family in Mary Poppins?",
      answer: "Banks",
      optionOne: "Williams",
      optionTwo: "Banks",
      optionThree: "Smith",
      optionFour: "Wilson",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      triviaQuestion:
        "Let it Go' is a song from which famous Disney Animated Movie?",
      answer: "Frozen",
      optionOne: "Toy Story",
      optionTwo: "Pinocchio",
      optionThree: "Aladdin",
      optionFour: "Frozen",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      triviaQuestion: "Gaston is the Villian in Which Disney Movie?",
      answer: "Beauty & The Beast",
      optionOne: "Beauty & The Beast",
      optionTwo: "Frozen",
      optionThree: "Tangled",
      optionFour: "Inside Out",
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      triviaQuestion:
        "How Many Cups are in 1 Pint?",
      answer: "2",
      optionOne: "3",
      optionTwo: "2",
      optionThree: "4",
      optionFour: "6",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      triviaQuestion:
        "Which of the Following is not a member of the stone fruit family?",
      answer: "Strawberry",
      optionOne: "Cherry",
      optionTwo: "Plums",
      optionThree: "Strawberry",
      optionFour: "Peach",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      triviaQuestion:
        "What is the main ingredient in the French Stew Bouillabaisse?",
      answer: "Seafood",
      optionOne: "Seafood",
      optionTwo: "Broth",
      optionThree: "Onion",
      optionFour: "Potato",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      triviaQuestion:
        "What Year did the TV Show Spongebob Squarepants start Airing?",
      answer: "1999",
      optionOne: "1999",
      optionTwo: "2005",
      optionThree: "2000",
      optionFour: "2010",
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      triviaQuestion:
        "Ketchup is a sauce traditionally with a base of what ingredient?",
      answer: "Tomato",
      optionOne: "Celery",
      optionTwo: "Lemons",
      optionThree: "Tomato",
      optionFour: "Onion",
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      triviaQuestion:
        "What is the Color of the arrow in the Go Square in Monopoly?",
      answer: "Red",
      optionOne: "Red",
      optionTwo: "Blue",
      optionThree: "Green",
      optionFour: "Yellow",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      triviaQuestion: "In Chess, which piece can only move in an L-Shape",
      answer: "Knight",
      optionOne: "Rook",
      optionTwo: "Knight",
      optionThree: "Queen",
      optionFour: "Pawn",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      triviaQuestion:
        "In a Game of Sorry!, How Many Pawns does each Player Have?",
      answer: "4",
      optionOne: "4",
      optionTwo: "6",
      optionThree: "2",
      optionFour: "1",
    },
    {
      id: 15,
      triviaQuestion:
        "In a Game of Uno, How many cards does each player start with?",
      answer: "7",
      optionOne: "4",
      optionTwo: "7",
      optionThree: "3",
      optionFour: "8",
    },
    {
      id: 16,
      triviaQuestion:
        "In a Game of Connect Four, How many Checkers does each Player Have?",
      answer: "21",
      optionOne: "12",
      optionTwo: "22",
      optionThree: "21",
      optionFour: "6",
    },
    {
      id: 17,
      triviaQuestion:
        "How many years of college do you need for a bachelors?",
      answer: "4",
      optionOne: "3",
      optionTwo: "1",
      optionThree: "5",
      optionFour: "4",
    },
    {
      id: 18,
      triviaQuestion: "What sort of musical instrument is a 'fiddle'",
      answer: "Violin",
      optionOne: "Guitar",
      optionTwo: "Flute",
      optionThree: "Chello",
      optionFour: "Violin",
    },
    {
      id: 19,
      triviaQuestion: "The Music Mamma Mia! is based on Whose Music?",
      answer: "Abba",
      optionOne: "Abba",
      optionTwo: "Maroon 5",
      optionThree: "The Platters",
      optionFour: "Beach Boys",
    },
    {
      id: 20,
      triviaQuestion:
      "Which of these musical instruments is played by plucking or strumming?",
      answer: "Banjo",
      optionOne: "Violin",
      optionTwo: "Guitar",
      optionThree: "Banjo",
      optionFour: "Chello",
      },
    ];